I am in my head.
You live in your head.
How does that go with the growth?
It's a challenge.
The side that has been serving me most is being so in my, I can't help be self-aware.
I feel everything.
It's a gift and a curse.
Yeah, exactly.
It's very, it's very toxic.
I wish, it's tough because I don't like pity, but often I want, I want to be like, if you
knew what I was going through in my, I am so like high functioning.
If you knew, you wouldn't say to me.
It would be so nice.
It's like, if you're doing it, then you can't ask for credit because you're doing it.
If I don't have legs, like I can't walk.
Can you help me?
And I got to say yes.
But if I'm walking and you're like, I can't, I'm having, I'm struggling walking.
I'd be like, nigga, you walk from here to there.
You're good.
So.